Welcome back, y'all. This is The Amanda Seale Show.
I'm Amanda Seales, and it's time for us to go
Fiki Fiki for the record with our headliner of the week,
the comedian, actor, writer, producer, James Davis.
What is a song that describes your life right now?
It's a cheesy shine on them.
Pretty much, she's talking about, like, you know,
people be hatin'.
People be hatin'.
But you gotta keep on shining on them.
When it comes to haters, do you feel like you have,
like, a hater abundance?
I don't feel like there's a bunch of people
who, like, hate James comedy.
I feel like I don't have haters, I have sleepers.
Okay.
You know, I have a lot of sleepers,
and your sleep is hatin' on my money.
You said that you, like, basically carved out
your own world there, so I wanna know,
what's a song that speaks to your college years?
Montel Jordan, this is how we do it.
I feel like that played every time I walked
into somebody's door room. It was like,
this is how we do it.
It could be the cafeteria. Oh, shit.
This is how we do it.
Basketball game, division three, we're gonna lose.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Yeah.